University of Connecticut, Vice President for Academic Affairs Office Records [Anthony DiBenedetto and Julius A. Elias, 1981-1988] 1998.0154
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
University of Connecticut, Vice President for Academic Affairs Office Records [Anthony DiBenedetto and Julius A. Elias, 1981-1988]
undated, 1960-1991.
1998.0154
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
60.5 Linear feet
The Vice President for Academic Affairs, formerly the Provost, is the chief academic officer of the University and reports directly to the University President. The following University officers report to the Vice President for Academic Affairs: Assistant and Associate Provosts, Deans of Schools and Colleges, and the Directors of the Computer Center, Fiscal Services, Institutional Research, and the University Libraries.
University of Connecticut. Vice President for Academic Affairs Office.
History
Anthony T. DiBenedetto was a Professor of Chemical Engineering at the University of Connecticut from 1972-1980, and served as Department Head from 1972-1977. In 1980, he was named Dean of the Graduate School and Vice President for Graduate Education and Research. In 1981, he became Vice President for Academic Affairs.
Julius A. Elias, who served as Interim Vice President for Academic Affairs (1986-1988), was a professor of Philosophy at the University of Connecticut from 1975-1986, as well as Dean of the College of Liberal Arts and Sciences, and Coordinator of the Division of National Defense Training.
Scope and Content
This collection includes the Vice President for Academic Affairs Office records during the administrations of Anthony T. DiBenedetto, Vice President from 1981-1989 and his successor, Julius A. Elias, who served as Interim Vice President from 1986 through 1988. The collection contains administrative, legal, fiscal and operation documents concerning the academic programs of the University from 1983-1989.
Arrangement
Series I: Subject Files ( undated, 1975-1989 ) contains the general files of the Vice President for Academic Affairs including information on the budget, tuition, institutional research, and the Honors, Student Abroad, and Women's Study programs.
Series II: President's Office ( 1981-1989 ) contains files relating to that office, as well as information on Affirmative Action Programs, the Development Office, and the UConn Foundation.
Series III: Vice President For Finance And Administration ( undated, 1974-1992 ) contains files relating to that office on such topics as budget, computerization, facilities, grants, personnel, and public safety.
Series IV: Vice President For Student Affairs ( 1975-1989 ) includes files on admissions and student activities.
Series V: Vice President For Student Health Affairs ( 1981-1989 ) contains files regarding the Health Center and Health Services Division, as well as the Travelers Center on Aging.
Series VI: Vice President For External Affairs ( 1985-1991 ) includes files relating to that office, as well as information on the Development Office and government relations.
Series VII: Registrar's Office ( 1982-1989 ) contains information on such topics as enrollment and scheduling.
Series VIII: Regional Campuses ( 1983-1989 ) is arranged in six subseries: Avery Point, Hartford, General, Stamford, Torrington, and Waterbury. Included within each subseries are topics such as budget, development, and task forces. General includes annual reports from the regional campuses, as well as files on such topics as food services.
Series IX: Boards ( 1984-1989 ) is arranged in two subseries: Board of Governors for Higher Education and Boards of Trustees. Board of Governors for Higher Education contains agendas and budget information, and is arranged alphabetically. Boards of Trustees contains information about four separate State Colleges and the Board of Trustees for Regional Community Colleges.
Series X: Senate ( 1975-1989 ) contains information about the University Senate, including minutes, correspondence, and files on committees and subcommittees.
Series XI: Schools and Colleges ( undated, 1980-1990 ) is arranged in thirteen subseries: College of Agriculture and Natural Resources, Schools of Allied Health Professionals, School of Business Administration, School of Dental Medicine, School of Education, School of Family Studies, Graduate School, School of Law, College of Liberal Arts and Sciences, School of Medicine, School of Nursing, School of Pharmacy, and School of Social Work. Each subseries is arranged alphabetically, and contains information about deans and department within each school or college, as well as information on accreditation, programs, and budget.
Series XII: Centers ( undated, 1982-1990 ) contains information regarding twenty-three centers located at the University.
Series XIII: Institutes ( 1960-1989 ) includes files on the Marine Sciences Institute, the Institute of Material Science, the Institute for Social Inquiry, and the Water Resources Institute.
Series XIV: Library ( 1970-1989 ) contains information about the University Library, with files on holding such as the Dodd Papers and the Ginsberg Archives; as well as data on fees and security.
Series XV: Research Foundations ( undated, 1983-1989 ) includes files on Connecticut Technology Park and the Research Advisory Council. The series is arranged alphabetically.
Series XVI: Committees ( undated, 1974-1987 ) contains files on university committees dealing with such issues as honorary degrees, collective bargaining, and staff development. The series is arranged alphabetically.
Series XVII: Long Range Planning Reports ( 1983 ) is a collection of Long Range Planning Reports from the schools, colleges, and regional campuses of the University. There is also a report called Opportunities for the '80s.
Series XVIII: Department of Higher Education ( 1979-1989 ) contains proposals, reports, and similar materials documenting the activities of the University with the Department.
Series XIX: Non-University Organizations and Outside Agencies ( undated, 1978-1989 ) include files on such groups as the American Association of University Professors, the Council of Presidents, NASULGC, and NEBHE, as well as the Yale University Visiting Faculty Program. Information on other universities and various foundations is also included here.
Bibliography
Acquisition Information
The records of the Office of the Vice President for Academic Affairs, 1983-1989, were transferred to Historical Manuscripts and Archives (now Archives & Special Collections) from the Vice President for Academic Affairs Office in several accessions between 1989 and 1992.
Related Material
Archives & Special Collections has a substantial collection of materials pertaining to the University, its history, administration, faculty, staff and students. For detailed information on these collections please contact the curator or ask at the Reading Room desk.
Access
The collection is open and available for research.
Administrative Records.; Correspondence.; Financial Records.; Minutes.; Notes.; Photocopies.; Publications.; Universities and colleges—United States—Administration.; Universities.; University of Connecticut. Office of the Vice President for Academic Affairs.; University of Connecticut—Administration.
- Series I: Subject Files, undated, 1975-1989
  - Academic advising, 1981-1985 (Box 1:, Folder 1)
  - Academic Plan: report on recommendations, 1986 (Box 1:, Folder 2)
  - Academic Planner, 1984 (Box 1:, Folder 3)
  - A.C.E. internship, 1985 (Box 1:, Folder 4)
  - Administrative interpretation, undated (Box 1:, Folder 5)
  - Asian-American issues, 1987-1989 (Box 1:, Folder 6-7)
  - Asian-American studies: A. Chiang report, 1988-1989 (Box 1:, Folder 8)
  - Assessing General Education, 1988 (Box 1:, Folder 9)
  - Associate deans, 1985 (Box 1:, Folder 10)
  - Athletics, 1985-1986 (Box 1:, Folder 11-13)
  - Award nominations, 1989 (Box 1:, Folder 14)
  - Benton Museum of Art, 1982-1989 (Box 1:, Folder 15-21)
  - Budget, 1984-1987 (Box 1:, Folder 22-26)
  - Burke Report, 1986, Fall (Box 1:, Folder 27)
  - By-laws/proposed amendments, undated (Box 1:, Folder 28)
  - Code of Ethics, 1984-1986 (Box 1:, Folder 29)
  - Code violations, undated (Box 1:, Folder 30)
  - Connecticut Department of Mental Retardation, 1986 (Box 1:, Folder 31)
  - Contingency Fund, undated (Box 1:, Folder 32)
  - Controller's Office, 1985 (Box 1:, Folder 33)
  - Core curriculum, 1986 (Box 1:, Folder 34)
  - Council of Deans, 1987-1988 (Box 1:, Folder 35)
  - Council on Academic Affairs: search for executive director, 1984 (Box 1:, Folder 36)
  - Dean's Council: housing for academic personnel, 1988 (Box 1:, Folder 37)
  - Emergency closing, 1988-1989 (Box 1:, Folder 38)
  - Emergency operations plan, undated (Box 1:, Folder 39)
  - Environmental Health and Safety, 1985 (Box 1:, Folder 40)
  - Escrow account 6012, 1987 (Box 1:, Folder 41)
  - Facilities Office, 1985 (Box 1:, Folder 42-43)
  - Faculty vitae, 1984-1985 (Box 1:, Folder 44)
  - Financial aid, 1985-1986 (Box 1:, Folder 45)
  - Foreign Teaching Assistants, 1985-1986 (Box 1:, Folder 46)
  - Fund for the Improvement or Post Secondary Education, 1988-1989 (Box 1:, Folder 47)
  - General, 1980-1989 (Box 2:, Folder 48-53)
  - General Education requirements, 1985-1986 (Box 2:, Folder 54)
  - Grants and Contracts Office, 1985-1986 (Box 2:, Folder 55)
  - Hazardous waste, 1982-1984 (Box 2:, Folder 56)
  - Honors Program, 1983-1989 (Box 2:, Folder 57-60)
  - Inaugural Symposium, 1985 (Box 2:, Folder 61)
  - Information Service Management: University Computer Systems, 1985-1986 (Box 2:, Folder 62-63)
  - Information Management System, 1985 (Box 2:, Folder 64)
  - Institutional Research, 1983-1986 (Box 2:, Folder 65-70)
  - Institutional Research Office, 1984-1989 (Box 2:, Folder 71-81)
  - International Education and Development Office, 1984 (Box 3:, Folder 82)
  - International Studies Program, 1988 (Box 3:, Folder 83)
  - International Studies at Stanford, Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 3:, Folder 84)
  - Krisch Report, 1987 (Box 3:, Folder 85)
  - Legislature, 1984-1986 (Box 3:, Folder 86)
  - Management Information Systems, 1985 (Box 3:, Folder 87)
  - Mansfield Training School, 1987-1989 (Box 3:, Folder 88-89)
  - Mission statements, 1975-1976 (Box 3:, Folder 90)
  - Museum of Natural History, 1989 (Box 3:, Folder 91)
  - Personnel, 1985-1986 (Box 3:, Folder 92-94)
  - Position questionnaire: CRESAP, 1988 (Box 3:, Folder 95)
  - Program profile, 1988 (Box 3:, Folder 96)
  - Retrospective and goals: JAE, 1986-1987 (Box 3:, Folder 97)
  - Special Achievement Merit, 1986 (Box 3:, Folder 98)
  - Special projects: undergraduate laboratories, 1984 (Box 3:, Folder 99)
  - Study Abroad, 1985-1988 (Box 3:, Folder 100-103)
  - Telephone concerns, 1985 (Box 3:, Folder 104)
  - Tuition/fees, 1985-1987 (Box 3:, Folder 105-108)
  - University Computer Systems: Genesys software, undated (Box 3:, Folder 109)
  - UConn Educational Properties, Inc., 1983-1986 (Box 3:, Folder 110)
  - Women's Studies Program, 1982-1989 (Box 3:, Folder 111-117)
- Series II: President's Office, 1981-1989
  - Affirmative Action Programs, 1984-1988 (Box 4:, Folder 118-122)
  - Alumni Association, 1984-1987 (Box 4:, Folder 123-124)
  - Development Office, 1983-1984 (Box 5:, Folder 125-137)
  - General, 1985-1989 (Box 5:, Folder 138-141)
  - Management and Budget Office, 1981 (Box 5:, Folder 142)
  - UConn Foundation, 1986-1989 (Box 5:, Folder 143-148)
  - University Publications, 1985-1986 (Box 5:, Folder 149)
  - University relations, 1985-1987 (Box 5:, Folder 150)
- Series III: Vice President of Finance and Administration, undated, 1974-1992
  - Budget, 1983-1986 (Box 6:, Folder 151-157)
  - Budget's Office, 1984-1992 (Box 6:, Folder 158-168)
  - Bursar's Office, 1984, 1990 (Box 6:, Folder 169-170)
  - Computer Application: Research Center, 1984 (Box 6:, Folder 171)
  - Computer Center, 1985-1987 (Box 6:, Folder 172-173)
  - Computerization issues, 1983-1985 (Box 6:, Folder 174-179)
  - Individual 5-year Computer Plan, undated (Box 6:, Folder 180-214)
  - Controller's Office, 1982-1988 (Box 7:, Folder 215-217)
  - Equipment Maintenance Fund, 1989-1990 (Box 7:, Folder 218)
  - Environmental Health and Safety, 1987-1990 (Box 7:, Folder 219-221)
  - Facilities Office, 1984-1990 (Box 7:, Folder 222-234)
  - Fee expenditures reduction, 1990 (Box 7:, Folder 235)
  - Financial aid, 1974-1984 (Box 7:, Folder 236-239)
  - General, 1982-1991 (Box 7:, Folder 240-247)
  - Gramm-Ruddman Hollings, 1986 (Box 7:, Folder 248)
  - Grants and Contracts: earned overhead, 1989-1991 (Box 7:, Folder 249)
  - Grants and Contracts Office, 1983-1991 (Box 7:, Folder 250-255)
  - Information Services Management, 1983-1984 (Box 7:, Folder 256-259)
  - Internal Auditing Office, 1980-1990 (Box 8:, Folder 260-263)
  - International Students and Scholars, Office of, 1987-1989 (Box 8:, Folder 264)
  - Jorgenson, 1988 (Box 8:, Folder 265)
  - Kleban Gift, 1987 (Box 8:, Folder 266)
  - Long-range campus land use, 1988 (Box 8:, Folder 267)
  - Management Salary Survey, 1987-1988 (Box 8:, Folder 268)
  - Managerial Comp Study, 1988 (Box 8:, Folder 269)
  - Mansfield Training School, 1989-1991 (Box 8:, Folder 270-272)
  - O.S.H.A., 1989 (Box 8:, Folder 273)
  - Outside consultant services, 1990 (Box 8:, Folder 274)
  - Personnel, 1983-1991 (Box 8:, Folder 275-281)
  - Ph.D./Business Administration, 1983-1985 (Box 8:, Folder 282)
  - Physical: Facilities Management Contract, 1990 (Box 8:, Folder 283)
  - Physical Plant: water system, 1991 (Box 8:, Folder 284)
  - Planning Office, 1990-1991 (Box 8:, Folder 285-286)
  - Public Safety Department, 1983-1991 (Box 8:, Folder 287-292)
  - Purchasing Department, 1983 (Box 8:, Folder 293)
  - Purchasing and Warehousing, 1986-1991 (Box 8:, Folder 294)
  - Revenues, 1991 (Box 8:, Folder 295)
  - 6.12 Fund, 1987-1991 (Box 8:, Folder 296)
  - Space, 1988-1990 (Box 8:, Folder 297)
  - Student labor rates, 1990 (Box 8:, Folder 298)
  - Technology Center, 1989 (Box 8:, Folder 299)
  - Telemedia contract, 1989 (Box 8:, Folder 300)
  - Travel, 1989-1990 (Box 8:, Folder 301)
  - Travel Advisory Committee, 1990 (Box 8:, Folder 302)
  - Tuition/fees), 1983-1991 (Box 8:, Folder 303-307)
  - UCEPI, 1983, 1989 (Box 8:, Folder 308-309)
  - University Computer Plan, 1986-1990 (Box 8:, Folder 310)
  - University fees, 1989-1990 (Box 8:, Folder 311)
- Series IV: Vice President for Student Affairs, 1975-1989
  - Admissions, 1983-1989 (Box 9:, Folder 312-318)
  - Cooperative Education, 1982-1986 (Box 9:, Folder 319-320)
  - Counseling Services Department, 1986-1987 (Box 9:, Folder 321)
  - Disabled Student Services Center, 1984-1986 (Box 9:, Folder 322)
  - General, 1984-1989 (Box 9:, Folder 323-327)
  - Residential Life, Department of, 1982-1989 (Box 9:, Folder 328)
  - Student Activities and Union Programs, Department of, 1975-1986 (Box 9:, Folder 329-330)
  - Undergraduate Student Government, 1989 (Box 9:, Folder 331)
- Series V: Vice President for Health Affairs, 1981-1989
  - Aids, 1986-1987 (Box 10:, Folder 332)
  - General, 1983-1989 (Box 10:, Folder 333-338)
  - Health Center, 1986-1989 (Box 10:, Folder 339-341)
  - Health Center, 1981-1989 (Box 11:, Folder 342-351)
  - Health Science Cluster Program, 1984-1986 (Box 11:, Folder 352-353)
  - Health Services Division, 1981-1989 (Box 11:, Folder 354-359)
  - Travelers Center on Aging, 1981-1989 (Box 11:, Folder 360-365)
  - University Affiliated Facilities, 1984-1987 (Box 11:, Folder 366-367)
  - Venture Capital Proposal, 1983-1984 (Box 11:, Folder 368)
- Series VI: Vice President for External Affairs, 1985-1991
  - Commencement, 1990-1991 (Box 12:, Folder 369)
  - Computing initiative, 1990 (Box 12:, Folder 370)
  - Development Office, 1985-1989 (Box 12:, Folder 371-372)
  - Foundation Account holders, 1989 (Box 12:, Folder 373)
  - General, 1989-1991 (Box 12:, Folder 374)
  - Governmental relations, 1987-1991 (Box 12:, Folder 375-379)
  - IBM, 1989 (Box 12:, Folder 380)
  - Institutional Relations, 1990 (Box 12:, Folder 381)
  - PC campaign, 1991 (Box 12:, Folder 382)
  - Publications, 1990-1991 (Box 12:, Folder 383)
- Series VII: Registrar's Office, 1982-1989
  - Catalog office, 1986-1987 (Box 13:, Folder 384)
  - Enrollment reports, 1984-1985 (Box 13:, Folder 385-386)
  - General, 1984-1989 (Box 13:, Folder 387-392)
  - Goals and functions of the Registrar's Office, 1982-1983 (Box 13:, Folder 393)
  - Registration procedure, 1983-1988 (Box 14:, Folder 394)
  - Scheduling office, 1983-1988 (Box 14:, Folder 395-397)
  - Touch tone telephone registration, 1987 (Box 14:, Folder 398)
- Series VIII: Regional Campuses, 1983-1989
  - Avery Point, 1983-1989 (Box 15:, Folder 399-407)
  - Hartford, 1983-1989 (Box 15:, Folder 408-425)
  - General, 1984-1988 (Box 15:, Folder 426-436)
  - Stamford, 1984-1988 (Box 16:, Folder 437-455)
  - Torrington, 1984-1986 (Box 16:, Folder 456-462)
  - Waterbury, 1983-1989 (Box 16:, Folder 463-470)
- Series IX: Boards, 1984-1989
  - Board of Governors for Higher Education, 1985-1989 (Box 17:, Folder 471-477)
  - Board of Governors for Higher Education, 1984-1989 (Box 18:, Folder 478-485)
  - Boards of Trustees, 1984-1985 (Box 18:, Folder 486-489)
- Series X: Senate, 1975-1989
  - Admissions Committee, 1983-1986 (Box 19:, Folder 490-491)
  - Budget Committee, 1980-1986 (Box 19:, Folder 492-493)
  - Curricula and Courses Committee, 1983-1986 (Box 19:, Folder 494-495)
  - Executive Committee, 1981-1989 (Box 19:, Folder 496-500)
  - Faculty Standards Committee, 1981-1987 (Box 19:, Folder 501-504)
  - Growth and Development Committee, 1983-1986 (Box 19:, Folder 505-506)
  - Minutes and correspondence, 1975-1989 (Box 19:, Folder 507)
  - Misconduct in Research and Scholarship Subcommittee, 1984-1987 (Box 20:, Folder 508-509)
  - Nominating Committee, 1984-1985 (Box 20:, Folder 510)
  - Planning Committee, 1983 (Box 20:, Folder 511)
  - Scholastic Standards Committee, 1983-1986 (Box 20:, Folder 512-513)
  - Undergraduate Counseling Subcommittee, 1982 (Box 20:, Folder 514)
- Series XI: Schools and Colleges, undated, 1980-1990
  - Agricultural and Natural Resources, College of
    - Agricultural Economics and Rural Sociology, Department of, 1982-1988 (Box 21:, Folder 515-517)
    - Agricultural Engineering, Department of, 1982-1984 (Box 21:, Folder 518)
    - Agricultural Experiment Station, 1983-1984 (Box 21:, Folder 519)
    - Agricultural Task Force, 1987-1989 (Box 21:, Folder 520-522)
    - Animal care, 1985-1989 (Box 21:, Folder 523-527)
    - Animal Genetics, Department of, 1982-1987 (Box 21:, Folder 528-530)
    - Animal Industries, Department of, 1982-1985 (Box 21:, Folder 531-533)
    - Animal Sciences, Department of, 1985-1989 (Box 21:, Folder 534-537)
    - Annual animal inventory, 1982-1989 (Box 21:, Folder 538-539)
    - Arboretum, 1983-1984 (Box 21:, Folder 540)
    - Budget and funding, 1988-1989 (Box 21:, Folder 541)
    - Code violations, 1988 October (Box 21:, Folder 542)
    - Cooperative Extension Service, 1981-1989 (Box 21:, Folder 543-549)
    - Creamery, 1989 (Box 21:, Folder 550)
    - Curricula and Courses Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 21:, Folder 551)
    - Dean, 1983-1989 (Box 21:, Folder 552-553)
    - Faculty meeting minutes, 1986 (Box 21:, Folder 554)
    - General, 1983-1989 (Box 21:, Folder 555-561)
    - Holcomb Farm, 1986-1988 (Box 21:, Folder 562)
    - Integrated Pest Management Program Proposal, 1985-1986 (Box 21:, Folder 563)
    - Microchemistry, Department of, 1989 April (Box 21:, Folder 564)
    - Nutritional Sciences, Department of, 1983-1988 (Box 21:, Folder 565-569)
    - Pathobiology, Department of, 1985-1989 (Box 22:, Folder 570-571)
    - Pathobiology: Spring Hill Farm, 1989 June (Box 22:, Folder 572)
    - Plant Science, Department of, 1983-1987 (Box 22:, Folder 573-575)
    - Plant Science: Bartlett Arboretum, 1988-1989 (Box 22:, Folder 576)
    - Ratcliffe Hicks School of Agriculture, 1982-1989 (Box 22:, Folder 577-578)
    - Renewable Natural Resources Department, 1985-1987 (Box 22:, Folder 579)
    - Renewable Natural Resources/Agricultural Engineering merger, 1987 (Box 22:, Folder 580)
  - Allied Health Professions, School of
    - Accreditation, undated (Box 22:, Folder 581)
    - Budget and funding, 1988-1989 (Box 22:, Folder 582)
    - Dean, 1985-1989 (Box 22:, Folder 583)
    - Faculty meeting minutes, 1985-1986 (Box 22:, Folder 584)
    - General, 1981-1988 (Box 22:, Folder 585-589)
    - Handicapped accessibility, 1987 (Box 22:, Folder 590)
    - Nursing relocation, 1983-1985 (Box 22:, Folder 591-592)
    - Nyack Hospital, 1987 (Box 22:, Folder 593)
    - Proposed Masters in Physical Therapy, undated (Box 22:, Folder 594)
    - Raising entry level education for physical therapists, 1985 (Box 22:, Folder 595)
    - Section 504 Transition Plan, 1981-1985 (Box 22:, Folder 596)
  - Business Administration, School of
    - Accounting, Department of, 1983-1989 (Box 22:, Folder 597-599)
    - Accreditation, 1983-1985 (Box 22:, Folder 600)
    - Budget and funding, 1988 (Box 22:, Folder 601)
    - Business Environment and Policy Department>, 1985-1989 (Box 22:, Folder 602-604)
    - Computer lab fee, 1989 (Box 22:, Folder 605)
    - Dean, 1983-1989 (Box 22:, Folder 606-610)
    - Doctoral Program Proposal, 1984-1988 (Box 22:, Folder 611-613)
    - Executive MBA, undated (Box 22:, Folder 614)
    - Faculty meeting minutes, 1985-1986 (Box 22:, Folder 615-616)
    - Finance Department, 1983-1988 (Box 22:, Folder 617-620)
    - General, 1983-1986 (Box 22:, Folder 621-624)
    - General, 1986-1989 (Box 23:, Folder 625-627)
    - Health Systems Management, Center for, 1984-1988 (Box 23:, Folder 628-630)
    - IBM Program, 1989 (Box 23:, Folder 631)
    - Information Management Department, 1983-1988 (Box 23:, Folder 632-635)
    - Management and Organization Department, 1983-1987 (Box 23:, Folder 636-637)
    - Marketing Department, 1985-1988 (Box 23:, Folder 638-639)
    - MBA Program, 1981-1989 (Box 23:, Folder 640-653)
    - Refurbishment, 1988 April (Box 23:, Folder 654)
    - Space utilization, undated (Box 23:, Folder 655)
    - Study of internal markets, 1987 (Box 23:, Folder 656)
    - Upper division status, 1983 (Box 23:, Folder 657)
  - Dental Medicine, School of
    - General, 1983-1984 (Box 23:, Folder 658)
  - Education, School of
    - Affiliated Program on Development Disabilities, 1987 (Box 23:, Folder 659)
    - Bilingual Fellowships, 1986 (Box 23:, Folder 660)
    - Budget and funding, 1986-1988 (Box 23:, Folder 661)
    - Cooperative Ph.D. Program, 1985-1986 (Box 23:, Folder 662)
    - Counseling Psychology Program, 1985 December (Box 23:, Folder 663)
    - Curriculum and instruction, 1985-1989 (Box 23:, Folder 664-665)
    - Dean, 1985-1989 (Box 23:, Folder 666-668)
    - Education Administration Department, 1986 (Box 23:, Folder 669)
    - Education Leadership Department, 1986-1987 (Box 23:, Folder 670-671)
    - Educational Psychology, 1985-1989 (Box 23:, Folder 672-675)
    - Educational Studies and Instructional Media, 1983-1989 (Box 23:, Folder 676)
    - E.O. Smith High School, 1983-1986 (Box 23:, Folder 677-680)
    - General, 1983-1989 (Box 23:, Folder 681-686)
    - Higher Technical and Adult Education Department, 1984-1986 (Box 24:, Folder 687-688)
    - Kellogg Foundation Grant information, 1987 (Box 24:, Folder 689)
    - Learning Disabilities Project, 1985-1988 (Box 24:, Folder 690-691)
    - Learning Disabilities Resources Center, 1984-1986 (Box 24:, Folder 692)
    - Merger: Educational Administration Office/Higher Technology and Adult Education Department, 1985 (Box 24:, Folder 693)
    - NCATE Program review, 1988-1989 (Box 24:, Folder 694)
    - Ph.D. Program with state universities, 1985-1989 (Box 24:, Folder 695)